const TreatQuestions = [
    {
      question: "Where can you find shelter during a tornado?",
      options: ["The basement", "In the attic", "The living room"],
      answer: 0, // index of the correct answer
    },
    {
      question: "What number do you call in an emergency if you need help from police, firefighters, or an ambulance?",
      options: ["911", "365", "123"],
      answer: 0,
    },
    {
      question: "What do you do if you think someone is following you?",
      options: ["Stop and ask them who they are", "Hide in an alley or bush", "Run to a public space and call an emergency contact"],
      answer: 2,
    },
    {
      question: "What do you do if the phone rings and a stranger asks about your name or address?",
      options: ["Tell them your name and address", "Hang up and tell a trusted adult about the call", "Scare them by telling them you're calling the police"],
      answer: 1,
    },
    {
      question: "What do you do if you’re locked outside of your home?",
      options: ["Wait outside until someone comes home", "Break in through a window", "Go to a trusted neighbor and call your guardian"],
      answer: 2,
    },
    {
      question: "What do you do in case an earthquake begins while you’re alone at home?",
      options: ["Hide underneath a table or desk and away from windows", "Hide next to a window", "Run outside to escape"],
      answer: 0,
    },
    {
      question: "What do you do if your clothes catch on fire?",
      options: ["Get in a bath or shower", "Stop, drop, and roll on the ground", "Run around until the fire stops"],
      answer: 1,
    },
    {
      question: "What do you do if there's a fire in your house?",
      options: ["Pour water on the fire", "Grab all of your toys and escape", "Run outside and call 911 and your emergency contacts"],
      answer: 2,
    },
    {
      question: "What do you do if your house starts flooding?",
      options: ["Open the door to escape the house", "Go to the roof or highest room and call 911", "Keep swimming so you don't drown"],
      answer: 1,
    },
    {
      question: "What do you do in the case you get a burn?",
      options: ["Run it under cold water and call an adult", "Put ice on it", "Rub your skin with lotion"],
      answer: 0,
    },
    {
      question: "What do you do if you get lost in a store and can't find your guardians?",
      options: ["Cry loudly until someones helps", "Go backwards to find them", "Call them on your phone or ask an employee for help"],
      answer: 2,
    },
    {
      question: "What do you do if you fall in water and don’t know how to swim?",
      options: ["Hold your breath", "Stay calm, float on your back, and call for help", "Wiggle to stay swimming"],
      answer: 1,
    },
    {
      question: "Who can you trust if you’re lost?",
      options: ["A police officer", "A stranger asking you to follow them", "A stranger who says they know you"],
      answer: 0,
    },
    {
      question: "What do you do if you accidentally break some glass?",
      options: ["Pick the pieces up with your hands", "Call an adult and stay away from it", "Put a towel over the broken glass"],
      answer: 1,
    },
    {
      question: "What should you do if someone is bullying you?",
      options: ["Say something mean to them", "Push or hit one time", "Ask a trusted adult to help you"],
      answer: 2,
    },
    {
      question: "When can you share pictures  online?",
      options: ["After asking a trusted adult", "When someone asks how you look", "When you want to share something cool "],
      answer: 0,
    },
    {
      question: "How do you safely cross a road?",
      options: ["Try to dodge the cars", "Cross anywhere after some cars pass", "Check both ways twice and cross at a crosswalk"],
      answer: 2,
    },

  ];
  
  export default TreatQuestions;
  